let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What do you call a file containing a program written in a high-level programming language?",
    answer: "A source file",
    options: [
      "A machine file",
      "A code file",
      "A target file",
      "A source file"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The \n digraph forces the print() function to:",
    answer: "break the output line",
    options: [
      "stop its execution",
      "duplicate the character next to the digragh",
      "break the output line",
      "output exactly two characters: \ and n"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "z = y = x = 1 print(x, y, z, sep='*')",
    answer: "1*1*1",
    options: [
      "1 1 1",
      "x*y*z",
      "1*1*1",
      "x y z"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following variable names are illegal? ",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "true",
      "anD",
      "TRUE",
      "True"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The ** operator:",
    answer: "performs exponentiation",
    options: [
      "does not exist",
      "performs duplicated multiplication ",
      "performs exponentiation",
      "perform floating-point multiplication"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "A data structure described as LIFO is actually a:",
    answer: "stack",
    options: [
      "list",
      "stack",
      "heap",
      "tree"
    ]
  },
      {
    numb: 7,
    question: "A list of package’s dependencies can be obtained from pip using its command named:",
    answer: "the argument’s name specified along with is value",
    options: [
      "deps",
      "show",
      "dir",
      "list"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "An operator able to check whether two values are equal is code as:",
    answer: "==",
    options: [
      "=",
    "!=",
      "==",
      "==="
    ]
  },
    {  
    numb: 9,
    question: "The pip list command presents a list of:",
    answer: "locally installed package",
    options: [
      "available pip commands",
      "outdated local package",
      "locally installed package",
      "all packages available at PyPI"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "A predefined Python variable that stores the current module name is called:",
    answer: "__name__",
    options: [
      "__name__",
      "__mod__",
      "__modname__",
      "__module__"
    ]
  },
];
